{"id": "ner_001", "text": "Apple Inc. was founded by Steve Jobs in Cupertino, California in 1976.", "tokens": ["Apple", "Inc.", "was", "founded", "by", "Steve", "Jobs", "in", "Cupertino", ",", "California", "in", "1976", "."], "labels": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "I-LOC", "O", "B-DATE", "O"]}
{"id": "ner_002", "text": "Elon Musk announced that Tesla will open a new factory in Austin, Texas next year.", "tokens": ["Elon", "Musk", "announced", "that", "Tesla", "will", "open", "a", "new", "factory", "in", "Austin", ",", "Texas", "next", "year", "."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "ner_003", "text": "The World Health Organization reported a new outbreak in São Paulo, Brazil on Monday.", "tokens": ["The", "World", "Health", "Organization", "reported", "a", "new", "outbreak", "in", "São", "Paulo", ",", "Brazil", "on", "Monday", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "I-LOC", "O", "B-DATE", "O"]}
{"id": "ner_004", "text": "Dr. Marie Curie received the Nobel Prize in Physics in 1903 for her research in Paris.", "tokens": ["Dr.", "Marie", "Curie", "received", "the", "Nobel", "Prize", "in", "Physics", "in", "1903", "for", "her", "research", "in", "Paris", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-AWARD", "I-AWARD", "O", "O", "O", "B-DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O"]}
{"id": "ner_005", "text": "Microsoft acquired GitHub for $7.5 billion in June 2018.", "tokens": ["Microsoft", "acquired", "GitHub", "for", "$7.5", "billion", "in", "June", "2018", "."], "labels": ["B-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-MONEY", "I-MONEY", "O", "B-DATE", "I-DATE", "O"]}
{"id": "ner_006", "text": "Amazon CEO Andy Jassy announced record profits for Q3 at the Seattle headquarters.", "tokens": ["Amazon", "CEO", "Andy", "Jassy", "announced", "record", "profits", "for", "Q3", "at", "the", "Seattle", "headquarters", "."], "labels": ["B-ORG", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-DATE", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "ner_007", "text": "The European Central Bank raised interest rates by 0.5% last Thursday in Frankfurt.", "tokens": ["The", "European", "Central", "Bank", "raised", "interest", "rates", "by", "0.5%", "last", "Thursday", "in", "Frankfurt", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERCENT", "O", "B-DATE", "O", "B-LOC", "O"]}
{"id": "ner_008", "text": "SpaceX launched the Falcon 9 rocket from Cape Canaveral at 2:15 AM EST.", "tokens": ["SpaceX", "launched", "the", "Falcon", "9", "rocket", "from", "Cape", "Canaveral", "at", "2:15", "AM", "EST", "."], "labels": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "B-PRODUCT", "I-PRODUCT", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-TIME", "I-TIME", "I-TIME", "O"]}
